<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>An enuoye from Thomas Smyth upon thaunswer of one W.G. ...</title>
            <author>Smyth, Thomas, servaunt to the Quenes most excellent Majestie.</author>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1540</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 8 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 2 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2012-10">2012-10 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A12560</idno>
            <idno type="STC">STC 22880.2</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC S2986</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">29632669</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">ocm 29632669</idno>
            <idno type="VID">28046</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A12560)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 28046)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1475-1640 ; 1861:8)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>An enuoye from Thomas Smyth upon thaunswer of one W.G. ...</title>
                  <author>Smyth, Thomas, servaunt to the Quenes most excellent Majestie.</author>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>1 sheet ([2] p.).   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>R. Wyer?,</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>[S.l. :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1540]</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>In verse.</note>
                  <note>Imprint information from STC (2nd ed.).</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of original in the Society of Antiquaries.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Gray, William.</term>
               <term>Ballads, English.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2011-07</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2011-07</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2011-08</date>
            <label>Pip Willcox</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2011-08</date>
            <label>Pip Willcox</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-05</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <body>
         <div type="poem">
            <pb facs="tcp:28046:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <head>¶ An Enuoye from Thomas Smyth vpon thaunſwer of one. W. G. Lurkyng in Lorrells Denne / for feare men ſhulde hym ſee.</head>
            <lg>
               <l>Whether I troll here, or troll ther, I wyll ſo troll aboute</l>
               <l>That in my trollynge, I do truſt, as you are, to trolle you oute.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>NOwe with no leſſe ſalutacyon, that to ſuch doth pertayne</l>
               <l>Vnto you I do preſent, this lytell poore treatyſe</l>
               <l>Wyllynge you to vnderſtande, and alſo to knowe playne</l>
               <l>I haue receyued, your lewde lybell, wherin you enterpryſe</l>
               <l>Both me and my doynges, full proudely to deſpyſe</l>
               <l>But bable what you lyſt / it ſkylleth not a whyt</l>
               <l>Remember well this worde, hereafter cometh not yet.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>¶ You ruffle, and you rayle, for malyce and deſpyte</l>
               <l>And as a ragynge ruffyen / your ſelfe you do ſhewe playne</l>
               <l>For as moche as you be greued, with that, that I dyd wryte</l>
               <l>Which I wyll neuer denye, but throughlye mayntayne</l>
               <l>Yet (as you wryte) in one poynte, you haue cauſe to complayne</l>
               <l>For that I ſpake but of lykelyhod / and wente but by geſſe</l>
               <l>Of the treſon in your herte / you knowynge there no leſſe.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>¶ If with the poynte of my penne, I do you ſo ſpurre and prycke</l>
               <l>That therby you be greued and greatly ſtyrred to yre</l>
               <l>Yet doubte I not to ſyt ſure / all though you wynche and kycke</l>
               <l>Faſt cloſed in my dewty / to ſaue me from the myre</l>
               <l>But in your flynges take hede, beware I ſaye the fyre</l>
               <l>Or ſome other galtrope / take thys prouerbe for a token</l>
               <l>The pot ſo often goeth forth / at laſt it commeth home broken.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>¶ You are angry that I my ſelfe / ſo openly declare</l>
               <l>My name playnly dyſcrybynge, and of my ſeruyce the pyth</l>
               <l>All honeſt men thynk, I ſhulde no leſſe, wherfore I ne care</l>
               <l>Though mad malyce moue you / to be deſpyted therwith</l>
               <l>Hit haue pleſed you, to compare, the cobbler with the ſmyth</l>
               <l>Your proude ſkorne wherin / is eaſye ynough to be founde</l>
               <l>Yet better is a cobbler than an ydell vagabounde.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>☞ In openynge my name and ſeruyce / this was myne entente</l>
               <l>In caſe that for my doynges, I were thought worthy blame</l>
               <l>Any other perſon gyltles therfore ſhuld not be ſhente</l>
               <l>Conſydred (as is well knowen) many be of my name</l>
               <l>Myne offyce therfore I added / and thought therin no ſhame</l>
               <l>Nether braggynge, nor boſtynge / as to my charge you laye</l>
               <l>Who is naught hymſelfe / ſo iudgeth in others alwaye.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>¶ A true man ſhameth neuer, to ſhewe his name and face</l>
               <l>A thefe hym ſelfe myſtruſteth and is euermore in doubte</l>
               <l>Leſt that his lewde lyuynge / ſhulde preſent it ſelfe in place</l>
               <l>As commenly it is ſene / at lenght trouth is tryed oute</l>
               <l>So in lykewyſe you / do ſeke all corners round aboute</l>
               <l>But it woll not helpe you, though a whyle there be delaye</l>
               <l>Tyme ſhall trye your colour, be it ruſſet, blacke / or graye.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>¶ Of rumblynge in ſcryptures / you do me moch reproue</l>
               <l>Well yf your wyttes do ſerue you / my doynges to amende</l>
               <l>Come forth and ſhew your face / as to honeſtye doth behoue</l>
               <l>And lay vnto my charge / what you can reprehende</l>
               <l>Nay / nay / I am ſure, you do it leſt intende</l>
               <l>In raylynge is your ruffe, in your ſpelunke whan ye ſyt</l>
               <l>But remember well this worde / hereafter commeth not yet.</l>
               <pb facs="tcp:28046:2" rendition="simple:additions"/>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>yſely you councell me / to ſome taylour to reſorte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>nge out of ſcrypture / my texte the better to frame</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ot hyde your ſecte / nor yet your brotherly ſorte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> for the deuyll) you ſhewe your ſelfe the ſame</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>urs / Cobblers / and Tylers / doctous of worthy fame</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>des / Ruffyens / and others / amongs whom you rynge your bell</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> lyke as you be / ſo ſet you forth your councell.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>rynge in your boldnes / you wolde your ſelfe a traytour proue</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> only pretens of my moſt deſyred fall</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ntenans of popery / you ſay I do moſt loue</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> yf you knowe trewe / than a traytour I maye you call</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> your concelement but I woll dryue you to the tryall</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> doynges ſhall appere / thoughe deferred for a ſpace</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap>. W. G. I dare well ſhewe my face</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>eſt of your raylynges / I woll as nowe omyte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> the purpoſe penyſſhe my tyme I woll not ſpende</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> naught / but declare <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> the lewde vſe of your wyt</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>at malyce of herte towardes other you pretende</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e no nother buckler / wherwith your ſelfe to defende</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>uketh your ſecte / or wolde refourme your hereſye</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> you ſtray<gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e he is a mayntaynour of popery.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> though you wolde hyde yourſelfs / yet men may eaſely knowe</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>yned hertes you do beare to God and our good Kynge</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e hath ordeyned lawes / whiche cleane to ouerthrowe</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> auayll is dayly taken / to euydent is the thynge</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>lde beware your ſecte for ſurely you wolde fayne brynge</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ther to rayne ouer vs yf you wyſte / by what ſhyfte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e we haue / herof / Reade of kynge Henry the fyfte</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>e maye we playnly fynde / what a deteſtable ſorte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> fayned hertes / agaynſt theyr kynge dyd ryſe,</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>nge to choſe another kynge / that wolde theym ſupporte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>r naughtye errours and mayntaynaunce of hereſyes</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> (who of his grace) euer prouydeth for his</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>che knowlege therof / that they had not theyr entente</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>fled / ſome taken / ſome were hanged on the gallowes and brente.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>che thynge I do deſyre / all true ſubiectes to regarde</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> god and our good kynge / to beare a due obedience</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ll falſe fayned hertes / I wiſhe the ſame rewarde</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>ke as thothers had / worthely / for theyr offence</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> we ſyt. W.G. marke well this ſentence</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>er that as you be / ſo haue you vſed your wytte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>berr well this worde / here after commeth not yet.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> aduenture ſyr. W.G. you wyll yet bragge and boſte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> from the ſcripturs you haue dryuen me cleane a waye</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e therin whan you dare / you ſhall come to your coſte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>h for cauſe conſyderable / a whyle I do lytell ſaye</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e to ryde you with a byt / ſhall dryue you from your playe</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ſe you holde downe your hed / that fayne you wolde bere a loft</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>woll ſo tramell your heles / youre pace ſhall be more ſofte.</l>
            </lg>
            <lg>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> for an ende (Eternall God) I beſeche the graunt longe lyfe</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ſperous contynuans / to Henry our moſt noble kynge</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>theryne our Quene alſo / his moſt Laufull Wyfe</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>nte betwene theym bothe / lyke other braunches to ſprynge</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>warde our Prynce) that moſt odor<gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ferous thynge</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> theym longe togither Lorde / and graunt theym all the blyſſe</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ngels inceſſantly / ſynge (Gloria in excelſis) Amen.</l>
            </lg>
            <closer>¶ God ſaue the Kynge.</closer>
         </div>
         <div type="reprise">
            <lg>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>ether I trolle here, or trolle there, I wyll ſo trolle aboute</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> my trollynge I do truſte, as you are, to trolle you oute</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>e ſelfe ſame perſon, who not withſtandynge your deſpyte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>eth not, nor ſhrynketh not playnely him ſelfe to wryte</l>
               <l>
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> Smyth, ſe<gap reason="illegible" resp="#OXF" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>uant to the Kynges Royall Maieſtye</l>
               <l>Clerke of the Quenes graces counſell (though moſt vnworthy)</l>
            </lg>
            <trailer>¶ Finis.</trailer>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
